iprospect.com 2014-12-06

# Privacy Policy | iProspect | Driving Digital Performance

iProspect is committed to respecting and protecting the privacy of all visitors to our website. Generally, you can browse through our website without giving us information about yourself. Yet, there are times when we do need to collect your personal information to provide services you’ve requested from us. Our privacy policy outlines how we collect and use your personal information.

We participate in the European Digital Advertising Alliance (EDAA) self-regulatory programme and adhere to the EDAA Principles for Online Behavioural Advertising.

**What information do you collect?**  
We collect your personal information, which includes, but is not limited to: your first and last name, email address, physical address, contact information, title, industry and other information.  We do not collect sensitive information, such as your political or religious beliefs, ethnic background, sexual preference, health or any other.

When you browse our website, you do so anonymously. We do log your IP address to give us an idea of which part of the website you visit and how long you spend there. Your IP address is not linked to any personal information unless you have shared this information through a form on our website.

We do use “cookies” to collect information about how you use our site Cookies are small packets of information stored by your web browser based on the websites you visit. These cookies do not contain personal information about you, but allow us to know how many times you visit our website or related websites.

**How do I opt out of cookies?**

Turning off cookies altogether can affect your browsing experience not just on iProspect.co.uk, but across other major sites such as Google, Facebook and Twitter and is not recommended. You should be aware that by turning them off, you lose settings information from websites and automatic authentication information – eg: you will need to manually login each time you visit Facebook.

Most modern browsers should allow you to see what cookies are stored on your computer and :

  * Block third party cookies
  * Block all cookies from specific websites
  * Block all cookies from being downloaded
  * Delete all cookies once you close your browser

The URL’s below will take you to the relevant sections in all major browsers if you still wish to proceed –

Google Chrome  
[http://support.google.com/chrome/bin/answer.py?hl=en&answer=95647](http://support.google.com/chrome/bin/answer.py?hl=en&answer=95647)

Firefox  
<http://support.mozilla.org/en-US/kb/Cookies>

Internet Explorer  
<http://support.microsoft.com/kb/196955>

Safari  
<http://docs.info.apple.com/article.html?path=Safari/5.0/en/9277.html>

Opera  
<http://www.opera.com/browser/tutorials/security/privacy/>

Safari iPhone and ipad  
<http://support.apple.com/kb/HT1677>

Android  
[http://support.google.com/mobile/bin/answer.py?hl=en&answer=169022](http://support.google.com/mobile/bin/answer.py?hl=en&answer=169022)

Blackberry  
<http://docs.blackberry.com/en/smartphone_users/deliverables/32004/Turn_off_cookies_in_the_browser_60_1072866_11.jsp>

Windows Phone  
<http://www.microsoft.com/windowsphone/en-us/howto/wp7/web/changing-privacy-and-other-browser-settings.aspx>

To opt out of Google Analytics:  
<https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout>

To find out more about cookies please visit the relevant website set out next to you country of origin below:

Country | Entity | Website(s)  
---|---|---  
United States | Network Advertising Initiative | <http://www.networkadvertising.org/choices/>  
Digital Advertising Alliance | [http://www.aboutads.info](http://www.aboutads.info/)  
United Kingdom | Your Online Choices | [www.youronlinechoices.com/uk](http://www.youronlinechoices.com/uk)  
Other European Countries | Your Online Choices | [www.youronlinechoices.com](http://www.youronlinechoices.com/)  
Any | All About Cookies | [www.allaboutcookies.org](http://www.allaboutcookies.org/default.html)  
  
**When do you collect my information?**  
We collect your information when you register for a whitepaper, case study, webcast, or download content, attend a seminar or participate in an online survey, or ask to be included in an email or other mailing list.

**What do you do with the information?**  
Because iProspect is a global company, we may share your personal information with our other global offices. All such entities are governed by this privacy policy or are bound by the appropriate confidentiality and data transfer agreements.

Your personal information is never shared outside iProspect without your permission.

**What about third-party sites?**  
Our website does link to other websites. We do not share your personal information with them and are not responsible for their privacy practices. Once you have left our website, we recommend you read the privacy policies of these third-party websites.

**Children’s Privacy**

We do not actively seek to collect information about children aged 12 or under, or create interest segments specifically designed for the purpose of targeting children.  If you have any concerns about your child’s privacy in relation to our services, or you believe that your child may have entered PII onto our website, please contact us at: [moreinfo@iProspect.com](mailto:moreinfo@iProspect.com).

**Have any questions?**  
If you have any questions, want to review, correct and/or delete your personal information from our database, or wish to make a complaint, please email [ **moreinfo@iProspect.com**](mailto:moreinfo@iProspect.com).
